Guide to the Duke Endowment Archives, 1902-2018 and undated, bulk 1925-2006 RL.00332
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Rural Church Division Series (RESTRICTED), 1918-2006 and undated, 152 boxes
  - Building Grant Files Subseries, 1920-2006 and undated
    - Rockwell Church, Rowan County, 1968-1972 (Box RCD 96)
    - Rockwood Church, Haywood County, 1937-1939, 1977-1980, 2 folders (Box RCD 96)
    - Rocky Mount Church, Iredell County, 1927-1970, 1976-1983 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 97)
    - Rocky Point Church, Pender County, 1960-1963, 2 folders (Box RCD 97)
    - Rocky Ridge Church, Cabarrus County, 1909-1976 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 97)
    - Rocky Springs Church, Alexander County, 1926-1962 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 97)
    - Roe Church, Carteret County, and undated (Box RCD 97)
    - Rolling Hills Church, Union County, 1964-1966 (Box RCD 97)
    - Ronda Church, Wilkes County, 1927-1931 and undated (Box RCD 97)
    - Rones Chapel, Duplin County, 1945, n.d (Box RCD 97)
    - Rose Chapel, Iredell County, 1921-1968 and undated (Box RCD 97)
    - Rose Hill Church, Duplin County, 1926-1936 and undated (Box RCD 97)
    - Rose Hill Church, Duplin County, 2002-2005 (Box RCD 150)
    - Roseboro Church, Sampson County, 1977-1981 1988-1990, 2 folders (Box RCD 97)
    - Roseland Church, Moore County, 1939 (Box RCD 97)
    - Rosman Church, Transylvania County, 1954-1957 (Box RCD 97)
    - Rougemont Church, Durham County, 1924-1933, 1973-1974, 1983 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 97)
    - Rowland Church, Robeson County, 1927-1938 (Box RCD 98)
    - Royal Oaks Church, Cabarrus County, 1957, 1967-1975, 2 folders (Box RCD 98)
    - Ruffin Church, Rockingham County, 1936-1989 (Box RCD 98)
    - Rural Hall Church, Forsyth County, 1947-1951 and undated (Box RCD 98)
    - Rural Trinity Church, Mecklenburg County, 1928-1929 and undated (Box RCD 98)
    - Russell's Chapel, Lincoln County, 1953 (Box RCD 98)
    - Rutherford College Church, Burke County, 1929-1935 and undated (Box RCD 98)
    - Saint Andrews Church, Cumberland County, 1974 (Box RCD 98)
    - Saint Andrews Church, Guilford County, 1941-1947 (Box RCD 98)
    - Saint Andrews Church, Mecklenburg County, 1959 and undated (Box RCD 98)
    - Saint Andrews Church, Wake County, 1967-1972 and undated (Box RCD 98)
    - Saint Francis Church, Bertie County, 1961-1965 and undated (Box RCD 98)
    - Saint Francis Church, Wake County, 1986-1989 (Box RCD 98)
    - Saint Home Church, Wilkes County, 1975 (Box RCD 98)
    - Saint James Church, Carteret County, 1957-1959, 1970, 2 folders (Box RCD 98)
    - Saint James Church, Forsyth County, 1976-1979 (Box RCD 98)
    - Saint James Church, Mecklenburg County, 1945-1946 (Box RCD 98)
    - Saint James Church, Wake County, 1961, 1970, 3 folders (Box RCD 98)
    - Saint John's Church, Catawba County, 1975 (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint John's Church, Dare County, 1929-1976, 1990-1991 and undated, 3 folders (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint John's Church, Scotland County, 1947-1958 and undated (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint Luke Church, Scotland County, 1966-1969, 1980-1986, 3 folders (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint Luke's Church, Alamance County, 1962-1963, 1978-1984, 2 folders (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint Luke's Church, Burke County, 1960-1962 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint Mark Church, Forsyth County, 1946-1968 and undated (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint Mark Church, McDowell County, 1960-1968 and undated (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint Mark's Church, Gaston County, 1969-1978 (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint Mark's Church, Randolph County, 1987-1988 (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint Mary's Church, Randolph County, 1978-1982 (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint Mary's Church, Stokes County, 1985-1986 (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint Matthew's Church, Burke County, 1948-1950, n.d (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint Matthews Church, Cumberland County, 1959-1960 (Box RCD 99)
    - Saint Paul Church, Catawba County, 1946-1969 (Box RCD 100)
    - Saint Paul Church, Cleveland County, 1929-1946 and undated (Box RCD 100)
    - Saint Paul Church, Columbus County, 1934-1935 and undated (Box RCD 100)
    - Saint Paul Church, Iredell County, 1981-1982 (Box RCD 100)
    - Saint Paul Church, Nash County, 1980-1982 (Box RCD 100)
    - Saint Paul Church, Onslow County, 1972 (Box RCD 100)
    - Saint Paul Church, Richmond County, 1935-1938 (Box RCD 100)
    - Saint Paul's Church, Cabarrus County, 1951-1952 (Box RCD 100)
    - Saint Peter's Church, Carteret County, 1961, 1972, 2 folders (Box RCD 100)
    - Saint Peter's Church, Cleveland County, 1926-1951 and undated (Box RCD 100)
    - Saint Timothy, Transylvania County, 1961-1973, 2 folders (Box RCD 100)
    - Saint Timothy's Church, Davidson County, 1961-1970, 1984, 3 folders (Box RCD 100)
    - Salem Church, Alamance County, 1949-1950, 1985-1987; 2 folders (Box RCD 100)
    - Salem Church, Buncombe County, 1953 (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Burke County, 1980-1983 (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Cumberland County, 1952-1961 and undated (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Cumberland County, 2000-2004 (Box RCD 150)
    - Salem Church, Davie County, 1938-1972 and undated (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Granville County, 1928-1968 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Lincoln County, 1954-1955, 1970, 1983-1985, 3 folders (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Person County, 1941-1957 (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Pitt County, 1951-1954, 1987-1990, 2 folders (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Pitt County, 2002-2005 (Box RCD 150)
    - Salem Church, Randolph County, 1953 (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Robeson County, 1973-1982 (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Rockingham County, 1952-1955 and undated (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Rutherford County, 1928-1939 (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Sampson County, 1956-1960 (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Stanly County, 1955 (Box RCD 101)
    - Salem Church, Surry County, 1975-1977 (Box RCD 102)
    - Salem Church, Wayne County, 1946-1954 (Box RCD 102)
    - Salemburg Church, Wayne County, 1958-1959 (Box RCD 102)
    - Salter Path Church, Carteret County, 1943-1966, 1975-1980, 2 folders (Box RCD 102)
    - Saluda Church, Polk County, 1926-1954 (Box RCD 102)
    - Sandy Cross Church, Nash County, 1938-1955 and undated (Box RCD 102)
    - Sand Grove Church, Hoke County, 1954-1958 (Box RCD 102)
    - Sandy Plains Church, Anson County, 1925-1927 (Box RCD 102)
    - Sandy Plains Church, Robeson County, 1949-1950, 1970, 1980-1981 and undated, 3 folders (Box RCD 102)
    - Sandy Plains Church, Robeson County, 1997-2006 (Box RCD 150)
    - Sandy Ridge Church, Guilford County, 1944-1969 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 102)
    - Sandy Ridge Church, Stokes County, 1950-1960 (Box RCD 102)
    - Sardis Church, Buncombe County, 1927-1950, 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box RCD 102)
    - Sardis Church, Montgomery County, 1954 (Box RCD 102)
    - Sarecta Church, Duplin County, 1957 (Box RCD 102)
    - Saulston Church, Wayne County, 1965-1982, 2 folders (Box RCD 102)
    - Saxapahaw Church, Alamance County, 1941, 1971-1973, 1988-1990, 3 folders (Box RCD 102)
    - Scott's Hill Church, Pender County, 1931 (Box RCD 103)
    - Sea Gate Church, New Hanover County, and undated (Box RCD 103)
    - Sea Level Church, Carteret County, 1952-1953 (Box RCD 103)
    - Seaboard Church, Northampton County, 1931 and undated (Box RCD 103)
    - Sedge Garden Church, Forsyth County, 1940-1958, 1966-1978, 1986-1988 and undated, 3 folders (Box RCD 103)
    - Sedgefield Lakes Church, Guilford County, 1966-1984 and undated (Box RCD 103)
    - Selica Church, Transylvania County, 1980-1981 (Box RCD 103)
    - Semora Church, Caswell County, 1975-1982 (Box RCD 103)
    - Seven Springs Church, Wayne County, 1926-1951 (Box RCD 103)
    - Severn Church, Northampton County, 1951-1964, 2 folders (Box RCD 103)
    - Shady Grove Church, Burke County, 1961-1969, 1974-1984, 2 folders (Box RCD 103)
    - Shady Grove Church, Caswell County, 1926-1964 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 103)
    - Shady Grove Church, Davidson County, 1930-1961, 1989-1991 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 104)
    - Shady Grove Church, Granville County, 1957 (Box RCD 104)
    - Shady Grove Church, Haywood County, 1959-1961, 1984, 2 folders (Box RCD 104)
    - Shady Grove Church, Jones County, 1931-1958, 1982-1984, 3 folders (Box RCD 104)
    - Shady Grove Church, Warren County, 1926-1927 (Box RCD 104)
    - Shady Grove Church, Yadkin County, 1965-1974 (Box RCD 104)
    - Sharon Church, Brunswick County, 1940-1975 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 104)
    - Sharon Church, Cleveland County, 1930-1942 and undated (Box RCD 104)
    - Sharon Church, Currituck County, 1939-1959, 1971-1973, 2 folders (Box RCD 104)
    - Sharon Church, Forsyth County, 1966-1972 (Box RCD 104)
    - Sharon Church, Lenoir County, 1954-1958 (Box RCD 104)
    - Sharon Church, Northampton County, 1942-1955 (Box RCD 104)
    - Shiloh Church, Alamance County, 1952, 1979-1981 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 105)
    - Shiloh Church, Alleghany County, 1954-1955 (Box RCD 105)
    - Shiloh Church, Brunswick County, 1958-1983 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 105)
    - Shady Grove Church, Cabarrus County, 1963 (Box RCD 105)
    - Shiloh Church, Catawba County, 1945-1969 (Box RCD 105)
    - Shiloh Church, Columbus County, 1950-1953, 1967-1971, 2 folders (Box RCD 105)
    - Shiloh Church, Dare County, 1953-1973 (Box RCD 105)
    - Shiloh Church, Davidson County, 1958-1964, 2 folders (Box RCD 105)
    - Shiloh Church, Forsyth County, 1937-1965 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 105)
    - Shiloh Church, Iredell County, 1951-1953 (Box RCD 105)
    - Shiloh Church, Northampton County, 1957, 1962-1964, 1972-1976, 3 folders (Box RCD 105)
    - Shiloh Church, Rowan County, 1927-1958 and undated (Box RCD 105)
    - Shoal Creek Church, Jackson County, 1926-1930 (Box RCD 106)
    - Shoals Church, Surry County, 1943-1944 (Box RCD 106)
    - Sign Pine Church, Camden County, 1925-1931 (Box RCD 106)
    - Siloam Church, Surry County, 1930-1962 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 106)
    - Sims Church, Wilson County, 1954-1958 (Box RCD 106)
    - Singletary Church, Bladen County, 1932-1955 and undated (Box RCD 106)
    - Skyland Church, Buncombe County, 1938-1965, 2 folders (Box RCD 106)
    - Smethport Church, Ashe County, 1947-1963 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 106)
    - Smith's Church, Halifax County, 1942-1953; 1979-1983 (Box RCD 106)
    - Smith's Church, Robeson County, 1928-1930 and undated (Box RCD 106)
    - Smith Chapel, Columbus County, 1976-1981 (Box RCD 106)
    - Smith's Chapel, Wayne County, 1937-1970, 1979-1981 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 106)
    - Smith's Grove Church, Davie County, 1926-1959, 1971, 2 folders (Box RCD 106)
    - Smyrna Church, Carteret County, 1958-1959 (Box RCD 106)
    - Smyrna Church, Moore County, 1940, 1986-1988, 2 folders (Box RCD 106)
    - Snead's Ferry Church, Onslow County, 1925-1948 (Box RCD 107)
    - Snead's Grove Church, Scotland County, 1939-1954, 1962 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 107)
    - Snow Creek Church, Iredell County, 1958 (Box RCD 107)
    - Snow Hill Church, Buncombe County, 1941-1961, 1971-1976 and undated, 3 folders (Box RCD 107)
    - Snow Hill Church, Burke County, 1954-1955, 1982-1984, 2 folders (Box RCD 107)
    - Snow Hill Church, Gaston County, 1963-1967 and undated (Box RCD 107)
    - Snow Hill Church, Greene County, 1926-1934, 1980-1982, 1988-1990, 3 folders (Box RCD 107)
    - Snow Hill Church, Macon County, 1927-1941 (Box RCD 107)
    - Snow Hill Church, Stokes County, 1953, 1980-1982, 2 folders (Box RCD 107)
    - Soule Church, Hyde County, 1952-1953 and undated (Box RCD 107)
    - South Fork Church, Buncombe County, 1949-1953 and undated (Box RCD 107)
    - South Point Church, Gaston County, 1938-1951, 1985-1988, 2 folders (Box RCD 108)
    - South River Church, Alexander County, 1954 (Box RCD 108)
    - South River Church, Rowan County, 1945-1948, 1982-1983 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 108)
    - South Rosemary Church, Halifax County, 1949-1950 and undated (Box RCD 108)
    - Sparta Church, Alleghaney County, 1946-1951 (Box RCD 108)
    - Speedwell Church, Jackson County, 1952-1955 (Box RCD 108)
    - Speight's Chapel, Edgecombe County, 1958 (Box RCD 108)
    - Spring Hill Church, Davidson County, 1960-1968 (Box RCD 108)
    - Spring Hill Church, Harnett County, 1956-1966 (Box RCD 108)
    - Stacy Church, Carteret County, 1960, 1981-1986 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 108)
    - Staley Church, Randolph County, 1955-1961, 2 folders (Box RCD 108)
    - Stanford Church, Surry County, 1963-1967 and undated (Box RCD 108)
    - Stanhope Church, Nash County, 1954-1957 (Box RCD 108)
    - Stanley Church, Gaston County, 1939-1941 (Box RCD 108)
    - Stantonsburg Church, Wilson County, 1926-1929, 1977-1979, 2 folders (Box RCD 108)
    - Star Church, Montgomery County, 1925-1933 (Box RCD 108)
    - Steeleberry Church, Mecklenburg County, 1963-1965, 1972-1980, 3 folders (Box RCD 108)
    - Stem Church, Granville County, 1925-1936 (Box RCD 108)
    - Stephens Memorial Church, Ashe County, 1961, 2 folders (Box RCD 108)
    - Stewart's Church, Harnett County, 1951-1953 (Box RCD 109)
    - Stokes Church, Pitt County, 1938-1940 (Box RCD 109)
    - Stokesburg Church, Stokes County, 1955-1968, 1977-1980, 2 folders (Box RCD 109)
    - Stokesdale Church, Guilford County, 1930-1968, 1985-1988 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 109)
    - Stoneville Church, Rockingham County, 1926 (Box RCD 109)
    - Stonewall Church, Pamlico County, 1925-1961, 1989-1991 and undated, 3 folders (Box RCD 109)
    - Stony Hill Church, Stanly County, 1947-1964, 1978-1981 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 109)
    - Stony Knoll Church, Surry County, 1951 (Box RCD 109)
    - Stony Knoll Church, Yadkin County, 1977-1983, 2 folders (Box RCD 109)
    - Stony Point Church, Alexander County, 1928-1970 and undated (Box RCD 109)
    - Stovall Church, Granville County, 1989-1990 (Box RCD 109)
    - Straits Church, Carteret County, 1948-1954 (Box RCD 109)
    - Stumpy Point Church, Dare County, 1942-1943 (Box RCD 109)
    - Sulphur Springs Church, Cleveland County, 1926-1929, 1972-1975, 2 folders (Box RCD 110)
    - Summerfield Church, Guilford County, 1927-1955, 1976-1984, 3 folders (Box RCD 110)
    - Sunrise Church, Wake County, 2001-2004 (Box RCD 151)
    - Sunshine Church, Rutherford County, 1958-1959 (Box RCD 110)
    - Swannanoa Church, Buncombe County, 1938-1943 (Box RCD 110)
    - Swansboro Church, Onslow County, 1931-1936, 1967-1974, 1984-1986, 3 folders (Box RCD 110)
    - Swepsonville Church, Alamance County, 1934-1951 and undated (Box RCD 110)
    - Sylva Church, Jackson County, 1941-1977 and undated (Box RCD 110)
    - Tabernacle Church, Buncombe County, 1927-1930 (Box RCD 110)
    - Tabernacle Church, Forsyth County, 1939-1969 and undated (Box RCD 110)
    - Tabernacle Church, Greene County, 1945-1951 (Box RCD 110)
    - Tabernacle Church, Guilford County, 1967-1981, 2 folders (Box RCD 110)
    - Tabernacle Church, Guilford County, 2000-2005 (Box RCD 151)
    - Tabernacle Church, Moore County, 1937-1942, 1985-1987, 2 folders (Box RCD 110)
    - Tabernacle Church, Onslow County, 1953 (Box RCD 110)
    - Tabernacle Church, Randolph County, 1944, 1973-1976, 1988-1990, 3 folders (Box RCD 111)
    - Tabernacle Church, Scotland County, 1940, 1979-1981, 2 folders (Box RCD 111)
    - Tabernacle Church, Vance County, 1952 and undated (Box RCD 111)
    - Tabor Church, Cumberland County, 1926-1931 (Box RCD 111)
    - Tabor Church, Halifax County, 1941 (Box RCD 111)
    - Tanner's Grove Church, Rutherford County, 1940-1941 (Box RCD 111)
    - Taylorsville Church, Alexander County, 1955-1958, 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box RCD 111)
    - Temperance Church, Edgecombe County, 1951 (Box RCD 111)
    - Temple Hill Church, Wilkes County, 1954-1958 (Box RCD 111)
    - Thrift Church, Mecklenburg County, 1939-1965 and undated (Box RCD 111)
    - Tipton Hill Church, Mitchell County, 1942-1949 (Box RCD 111)
    - Topton Church, Cherokee County, 1925-1932 (Box RCD 111)
    - Transon Church, Ashe County, 1956-1958 (Box RCD 111)
    - Trenton Church, Jones County, 1955-1956, 1987-1989, 2 folders (Box RCD 111)
    - Trinity Church, Camden County, 1927-1955 and undated (Box RCD 111)
    - Trinity Church, Cumberland County, 1978-1983 (Box RCD 111)
    - Trinity Church, Franklin County, 1925-1965, n.d, 2 folders (Box RCD 111)
    - Trinity Church, Granville County, 1938-1943, 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box RCD 111)
    - Trinity Church, Guilford County, 1956-1957 (Box RCD 111)
    - Trinity Church, Iredell County, 1948-1966 and undated (Box RCD 111)
    - Trinity Church, Lenoir County, 1947, 1978-1985, 2 folders (Box RCD 112)
    - Trinity Church, McDowell County, 1956-1957 (Box RCD 112)
    - Trinity Church, Mecklenburg County, 1940-1959, 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box RCD 112)
    - Trinity Church, Sampson County, 1973-1975 (Box RCD 112)
    - Trinity Church, Stokes County, 1961-1967,1973-1984, 3 folders (Box RCD 112)
    - Trinity Church, Stokes County, 1996-2004 (Box RCD 151)
    - Trinity Church, Union County, 1979-1982 (Box RCD 112)
    - Trinity Memorial Church, Randolph County, 1960-1969, 1978-1983, 2 folders (Box RCD 112)
    - Triplett Church, Iredell County, 1925-1958, 1973-1983 and undated, 3 folders (Box RCD 112)
    - Troutman Church, Iredell County, 1926-1947 and undated (Box RCD 113)
    - Tuckaseegee Road Church, Iredell County, 1960 (Box RCD 113)
    - Tucker's Grove Church, Lincoln County, 1984-1987 (Box RCD 113)
    - Turkey Church, Sampson County, 1975-1976 (Box RCD 113)
    - Turnersburg Church, Iredell County, 1931 (Box RCD 113)
    - Tusquittee Church, Clay County, 1929-1964 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 113)
    - Tweed Chapel, Buncombe County, 1927-1936 and undated (Box RCD 113)
    - Tyro Church, Davidson County, 1926-1955, 1969-1972 (Box RCD 113)
    - Tyro Church, Davidson County, 2001-2005, 2 folders (Box RCD 151)
    - Union Church, Caswell County, 1979-1982 (Box RCD 113)
    - Union Church, Forsyth County, 1950-1951, 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box RCD 113)
    - Union Church, Harnett County, 1941-1974 and undated (Box RCD 113)
    - Union Church, Hertford County, 1952-1954 and undated (Box RCD 113)
    - Union Church, Pasquotank County, 1925 (Box RCD 113)
    - Union Church, Union County, 1959-1964 1976-1981 and undated, 3 folders (Box RCD 113)
    - Union Church, Wilkes County, 1937-1941 (Box RCD 113)
    - Union Chapel Church, Davie County, 1951-1965 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 113)
    - Union Chapel Church, Mecklenburg County, 1926-1927 and undated (Box RCD 113)
    - Union Chapel Church, Stanly County, 1950-1968 and undated (Box RCD 113)
    - Union Chapel Church, Vance County, 1947-1963 and undated (Box RCD 113)
    - Union Grove Church, Harnett County, 1972-1977, 1982-1984, 2 folders (Box RCD 114)
    - Union Grove Church, Iredell County, 1943-1958 and undated (Box RCD 114)
    - Union Grove Church, Iredell County, 2002-2004 (Box RCD 151)
    - Union Grove Church, Orange County, 1943-1972 and undated, 3 folders (Box RCD 114)
    - Unity Church, Duplin County, 1949-1950 and undated (Box RCD 114)
    - Unity Church, Rowan County, 1958-1959, 1988-1990, 2 folders (Box RCD 114)
    - Upward Church, Henderson County, 1988-1990 (Box RCD 114)
    - Uwharrie Church, Montgomery County, 1940-1965 and undated (Box RCD 114)
    - Vanceboro Church, Craven County, 1951-1952, 1983-1987, 3 folders (Box RCD 114)
    - Vandemere Church, Pamlico County, 1938-1943 (Box RCD 114)
    - Vanderburg Church, Iredell County, 1941-1976, 1985-1988 and undated, 3 folders (Box RCD 114)
    - Vass Church, Moore County, 1963-1966 (Box RCD 114)
    - Vernon Church, Martin County, 1946-1948 and undated (Box RCD 114)
    - Verona Church, Onslow County, 1933-1980 and undated (Box RCD 114)
    - Vickery Church, Guilford County, 1948-1958 and undated (Box RCD 115)
    - Victory Church, Cumberland County, 1948-1950 and undated (Box RCD 115)
    - Village Point Church, Brunswick County, 1952 (Box RCD 115)
    - Wade Church, Anson County, 1953 and undated (Box RCD 115)
    - Wake Forest Church, Wake County, 1937-1941, 1970-1975, 2 folders (Box RCD 115)
    - Walker Memorial Church, Wayne County, 1965-1967, 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box RCD 115)
    - Wallace Church, Duplin County, 1926-1942 and undated (Box RCD 115)
    - Wall's Church, Hoke County, 1981-1984 (Box RCD 115)
    - Walnut Cove Church, Stokes County, 1926-1927, 1971-1972 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 115)
    - Walnut Grove Church, Orange County, 1928- 1970 (Box RCD 115)
    - Walstonburg Church, Greene County, 1933-1965 and undated, 3 folders (Box RCD 115)
    - Wananish Church, Columbus County, undated (Box RCD 115)
    - Ware's Chapel Church, Beaufort County, 1949-1965 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 115)
    - Ware's Chapel Church, Beaufort County, 2001-2005 (Box RCD 151)
    - Ware's Chapel Church, Martin County, 1959-1964 (Box RCD 115)
    - Warren Plains Church, Warren County, 1929-1935 (Box RCD 115)
    - Warren's Grove Church, Person County, 1947-1951 and undated (Box RCD 115)
    - Warrensville Church, Ashe County, 1930-1952 (Box RCD 115)
    - Warrensville Church, Ashe County, 1995-2005 (Box RCD 151)
    - Warsaw Church, Duplin County, 1926-1957 (Box RCD 115)
    - Watha Church, Pender County, 1959-1960 and undated (Box RCD 115)
    - Watha Church, Pender County, 2000-2004 (Box RCD 151)
    - Watson's Chapel, Hyde County, 1949-1950 and undated (Box RCD 115)
    - Waxhaw Church, Union County, 1925-1939, 1975-1981, 2 folders (Box RCD 116)
    - Weaver's Church, Halifax County, 1950-1951 (Box RCD 116)
    - Weaverville Church, Buncombe County, 1927-1957 (Box RCD 116)
    - Webb's Chapel, Lenoir County, 1952, 1978-1983, 2 folders (Box RCD 116)
    - Webb's Chapel, Lincoln County, 1954 1971-1974, 2 folders (Box RCD 116)
    - Weddington Church, Union County, 1953, 1971-178, 2 folders (Box RCD 116)
    - Wells Spring Church, Rutherford County, 1976-1981, 1988-1991, 2 folders (Box RCD 116)
    - Wendell Church, Wake County, 1929-1937 (Box RCD 116)
    - Wentworth Church, Rockingham County, 1952 (Box RCD 116)
    - Wesley Chapel, Davie County, 1946-1951 and undated (Box RCD 116)
    - Wesley Chapel, Franklin County, 1955-1958, 1972-1974, 2 folders (Box RCD 116)
    - Wesley Chapel, Guilford County, 1954-1955 (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley Chapel, Iredell County, 1949-1965 and undated (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley Chapel, Rockingham County, 1979-1981 (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley Chapel, Stanly County, 1947-1972 and undated (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley Church, Camden County, 1946-1950 and undated (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley Church, Columbus County, 1972 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley Church, Duplin County, 1939 (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley Church, Pitt County, 1944-1949 and undated (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley Church, Vance County, 1952 and undated (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley Memorial Church, New Hanover County, 1938-1939 (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley Memorial Church, Tyrrell County, 1937-1939 (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesleyan Chapel, Pendler County, 1986-1989 (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesleyana Church, Jackson County, 1958-1960 (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley's Chapel, Catawba County, 1944-1950 and undated (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley's Chapel, Jackson County, 1954 (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley's Chapel, Sampson County, 1931-1934 and undated (Box RCD 117)
    - Wesley's Chapel, Tyrrell County, 1940 (Box RCD 117)
    - West Bend Church, Randolph County, 1936-1971, 2 folders (Box RCD 117)
    - West Chapel Church, Randolph County, 1942-1943 (Box RCD 117)
    - West End Church, Moore County, 1957-1958, 1983-1985, 2 folders (Box RCD 117)
    - West Jefferson Church, Ashe County, 1925-1956 and undated (Box RCD 117)
    - West Marion Church, McDowell County, 1941 (Box RCD 117)
    - Westover Church, Wake County, 1949-1950 and undated (Box RCD 117)